RYAN SYAHRUL MUHARAM

CONTACT

+62 8587 7250 355

ryansyahrulm@gmail.com

Kota Tasikmalaya, Jawa Barat

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ryansyahrulm

PROFILE

My name is Ryan Syahrul Muharam, I am 19 years old. I recently graduated from Sistem Informasi, Jaringan dan Aplikasi major in SMKN 2 Kota Tasikmalaya. and I a person who has an Interest in contributing/career in the world of IT, especially in the field of Network Security and Web Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FTTH TECHNICIAN INTERN (OCTOBER 2023 - DECEMBER 2023)

PT. Global Koneksi Investama

- Create a network design
- Installation and configuration
- Maintenance hardware and software
- Monitoring, ensure the network is in optimal condition.
- Troubleshooting, analyzing problems, repairing, and testing.

CCTV TECHNICIAN INTERN (JULY 2023 - SEPTEMBER 2023)

INDO CCTV

- Install, maintain, and repair CCTV systems, including cameras, DVRs, monitors, and associated cabling and hardware.
- Perform site surveys to determine optimal camera placement and ensure coverage of critical areas for surveillance.
- Configure and program CCTV systems for recording, including setting up motion detection.
- Troubleshoot and diagnose issues with CCTV systems, identifying hardware faults and software glitches.

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER INTERN (APRIL 2023 - JUNE 2023)

PT. Global Koneksi Investama

- Basic knowledge HTML, CSS, and javascript and Responsive Web Design.
- Using Javascript library such as ReactJS.
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability

EDUCATION

SMKN 2 KOTA TASIKMALAYA (2020-2024)

Sistem Informasi, Jaringan dan Aplikasi

CERTIFICATE

- Fortinet Certified Fundamental: Cybersecurity
- Fortinet Certified Associate: Cybersecurity

SKILLS

- Fortigate
- Basic HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- MS Office Tools (MS Word, MS Excel, MS Power Point)